<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Musical Structure App</string>
    <string name="library">Music Library</string>
    <string name="artists">Artists</string>
    <string name="artist_placeholder">Artist Name Here</string>
    <string name="songs">Songs</string>
    <string name="song_placeholder">Song Name Here</string>
    <string name="albums">Albums</string>
    <string name="album_placeholder">Album Name Here</string>

    <string name="now_playing">Now Playing</string>
    <string name="explain_library">Here on the library page the user will have access to all their
    music files, specifically they will have to choose which organizational method they wish to view those files
        with. The code in this section is relatively straightforward. Most of the implementation is already done.</string>
    <string name="explain_artists">On this activity the user will interact with a list of artists. Clicking
    on one of these entries would bring the user to another list activity. To implement this I would need
    some functionality that will scan the user\'s phone for media files and lists them together using their
    meta data. I would also need to be able to create a new Activity for each individual artist.</string>
    <string name="explain_albums">On this activity the user will interact with a list of albums. Clicking
    on one of these entries would bring the user to another list activity. To implement this I would need
    some functionality that will scan the user\'s phone for media files and lists them together using their
    meta data. I would also need to be able to create a new Activity for each individual album.</string>
    <string name="explain_songs">On this activity the user will interact with a list of songs. Clicking
    on one of these entries will make that song the now playing song. To implement this I would need
    some functionality that will scan the user\'s phone for media files and lists them together using their
    meta data. I would also need to be able to play a media file, I could use the Media Playback API. </string>
</resources>
